http://www.golfbidder.co.uk/help/222/privacy-and-security.html

In English
(Click Me)
Checkout
(Click Me)
Buy Golf Clubs
[+]
Drivers
[+]
Fairway Woods
[+]
Irons
[+]
Putters
[+]
Wedges
[+]
Hybrids
[+]
Sell Golf Clubs
[+]
Sell Golf Clubs
Golf Accessories
[+]
Golf Bags
[+]
+ Stand Bags
+ Cart Bags
+ Pencil Bags
Golf Balls
[+]
+ New Balls
+ Lake Balls
Pull Carts
[+]
Clicgear Push Carts
Pull Cart and Trolleys
Golf Gloves
[+]
Travel Gear
[+]
Travel Bags
Shoe Bags
GPS / Range Finders
[+]
GPS
Laser Range Finder
Package Sets
[+]
Men's Package Sets
Junior Package Sets
Ladies' Package Sets
Accessories
[+]
Golf Clothing
[+]
Sale
[+]
Sale and Clearance
Golf Apparel Collections
[+]
Golf Shoe Collections
[+]
Auctions
[+]
Auctions
You are here
:
Home Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
Filter
[-]
Buyer Info
[-]
Seller Information
[-]
Help and Information
[-]
International Sites
Your Personal Data:
What we need
Golfbidder will be what’s known as the ‘Controller’ of the personal data you provide to us. We collect personal data about you, which may include your contact details, transaction history, golf preferences and communication preferences.
Why we need it
We need your transaction history to process orders on your behalf, and to service subsequent warranty claims or issues. This information may also help us to suggest replacement equipment, which we feel may be appropriate for you. We need your contact details to fulfil and deliver your order as well as being able to contact you for service reasons. Your communication preferences will inform if you would like to receive marketing communications.
What we do with it
All the personal data we handle is processed by our staff in the UK however for the purposes of IT hosting and maintenance this information is located on servers within the European Union. No third parties have access to your personal data unless the law allows them to do so.
How long we keep it
We are required under UK law to keep your personal data (name, address, contact details, order details) for a minimum of 7 years after which time it will be destroyed. Your information we use for marketing and historical purposes will be kept with us until you notify us that you no longer wish to receive this information. More information on our retention schedule can be made available upon request.
What are your rights?
If at any point you believe the information we process on you is incorrect you may request to see this information and even have it corrected or deleted. If you wish to raise a complaint on how we have handled your personal data, you can contact us and we will investigate the matter.
If you are not satisfied with our response or believe we are not processing your personal data in accordance with the law you can complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO).
For Data Protection queries, please contact Golfbidder Limited, Unit E5 Barwell Business Park, Leatherhead Road, Chessington, Surrey, KT9 2NY.
Kalrna Payments.
In order to be able to offer you Klarna’s payment options, we will pass to Klarna certain  aspects of your personal information, such as contact and order details, in order for  Klarna to assess whether you qualify for their payment options and to tailor the payment  options for you.
General information on Klarna you can find here. Your personal data is handled in  accordance with applicable data protection law and in accordance with the information in Klarna’s privacy policy.
Sell Your Golf Clubs
** FREE COLLECTION **
Sell Using Cash For Clubs
Klarna Pay In 3
No Interest. No Fees.
No Credit Application.
Keep up-to-date with the latest news and updates from Golfbidder.
[+]
[+]
[+]
[+]
